Pest control, 8 million, patient 12 million this year,
relatively good margins.
Yep. Yes, sir.
We have a marketing agency,
we're paying about a hundred grand a year.
Okay.
We want to pull that marketing in-house,
but we don't want to lose performers.
What would you do if you were in my shoes?
Why?
I just feel like there's a disconnect there somewhere.
Were they performing?
It seems to be doing all right, yeah.
I just feel like we can get a better LTV.
I'll give this as a rule of thumb in general for me.
I will typically never stop flows.
Right.
I'll just add flows.
So it's like, okay, we've got this marketing agency.
It's like, cool, we can hire two more marketing agencies
and they can all market for me.
I'll probably not make less money.
And then like, we also want to build it in-house.
Cool, we'll also build it in-house.
Like more promotion almost never makes you less money
provided you have a product that has gross margin
and makes sense.
Why not just start marketing and not cancel them?
Can do that too?
Yeah.